[
  {
    "question": "What is the primary goal of using Mohr’s method in this experiment?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Measure sodium concentration",
      "b": "Determine chloride content",
      "c": "Assess water color",
      "d": "Analyse pH levels"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is chloride concentration generally higher in wastewater compared to raw water?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Due to the presence of sodium chloride in diets",
      "b": "Industrial processes",
      "c": "Seawater leakage",
      "d": "All of the above"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of dilute nitric acid in the experiment?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Increase sample acidity",
      "b": "Enhance color changes",
      "c": "Neutralize the sample",
      "d": "Accelerate the titration process"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which solution is commonly used as an indicator in Mohr’s method?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Sodium hydroxide",
      "b": "Silver nitrate",
      "c": "Potassium permanganate",
      "d": "Potassium chromate"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the formation of a red-brown precipitate indicate in Mohr's method?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Endpoint of the titration",
      "b": "Sample contamination",
      "c": "Acidic conditions",
      "d": "None of the above"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "In potable water, what influences the perception of a salty taste due to chloride concentration?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Weather conditions",
      "b": "Sodium cation presence",
      "c": "Chloride levels below 100 mg/L",
      "d": "Calcium and magnesium predominance"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why might chloride concentrations harm metallic pipes and structures?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Enhance structural integrity",
      "b": "Cause corrosion",
      "c": "Accelerate aging",
      "d": "Improve conductivity"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary source of chloride in wastewater from human consumption?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Drinking water",
      "b": "Sodium chloride in diets",
      "c": "Atmospheric deposition",
      "d": "Industrial discharge"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method is used to determine chloride content in this experiment?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Gravimetric analysis",
      "b": "Mohr’s method",
      "c": "Spectrophotometry",
      "d": "Gas chromatography"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can the chloride concentration in brackish water be described?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "High",
      "b": "Low",
      "c": "Variable",
      "d": "Constant"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c"
  }
]
